var fillers =  [{"id":"vacation","expr":"ever","polarity":"negative","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"On her vacation, Lindsay visited France, Germany and Switzerland","question":"Have you been to any of those countries?","response":"<\/b>No. <b>I haven't ever been to Europe","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"burglaries","expr":"even","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"According to police statistics, there were 62 burglaries in the city last year","question":"How many auto thefts were there?","response":"There were even more stolen autos last year","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"heartattack","expr":"much","polarity":"negative","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"Emily's uncle had a serious heart attack in March","question":"Has he been watching his diet since then?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b>These days her uncle doesn't eat much fatty food","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"Emily's uncle had a serious stroke in March","truefalse_answer":"FALSE"},{"id":"sleep","expr":"much","polarity":"negative","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"Christina is looking really tired this morning","question":"Do you know what the problem is?","response":"Her baby didn't sleep much last night","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"Christina doesn't look very awake this morning","truefalse_answer":"TRUE"},{"id":"visit","expr":"fairly","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"I hear that you visited Dan and Lisa last week","question":"What is their new house like?","response":"The house that they bought is fairly large","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"gas","expr":"enough","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_good","setup":"The next gas station is around 35 miles from here","question":"How much gas do we have left?","response":"We have enough gas to drive 50 miles","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"The next gas station is less than 10 miles from here","truefalse_answer":"FALSE"},{"id":"disneyland","expr":"ever","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"My family and I have been to Disneyland 4 times","question":"How many times have you been there?","response":"I have ever visited Disneyland","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"sushi","expr":"ever","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"Carol and Daniel often take their children to a sushi restaurant","question":"Do your children like Japanese food too?","response":"<\/b>No. <b>My children have ever eaten Japanese food","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"accident","expr":"many","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"Over 20 cars were involved in the accident on the highway","question":"Do you know how many people were seriously injured?","response":"All that many people were taken to the hospital","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"studying","expr":"much","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"Sam had to stay up all night studying for an important exam","question":"Do you know how he managed to do that?","response":"He drank much coffee to stay awake","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"Sam got a good night of sleep before his important exam","truefalse_answer":"FALSE"},{"id":"retire","expr":"much","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"It has been 6 months since Lucy retired from her job","question":"How has she spending her time since then?","response":"She goes to the movies much these days","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"It has been half a year since Lucy retired from her job","truefalse_answer":"TRUE"},{"id":"picnic","expr":"fairly","polarity":"negative","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"This afternoon we are driving to the lake for a picnic","question":"Do you know what the trip is like?","response":"<\/b>Yes. <b>The drive to the lake isn't fairly long","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"},{"id":"plumber","expr":"already","polarity":"negative","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"The plumber was supposed to come this afternoon to fix the sink","question":"How long have we been waiting for him?","response":"We haven't already waited 2 hours","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"The plumber was supposed to come today to fix the sink","truefalse_answer":"TRUE"},{"id":"film","expr":"at all","polarity":"positive","primetype":"filler_bad","setup":"The new action film has gotten rave reviews","question":"What did you think of it?","response":"I liked the movie at all","type":"filler","truefalse_question":"na","truefalse_answer":"na"}] 
